JUAN LOPEZ

Data Analyst

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Argentina

EMAIL

juanjo-full@hotmail.com

LINKS

<u>Github</u>

<u>linkedin</u>

SKILLS

Effective Time Management

Adaptability

Fast Learner

Communication Skills

Problem Solving Skills

Critical Thinking Skills

PROFILE

Data analyst with over one year of experience in data analysis with a growing passion to Machine learning and Data Science I worked as a remote IA content creator for a curated art house In the US, teaching the state of art of AI, and their usage

Actually working as an educator, in DGCyE in Buenos aires.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Al content creator, educator, Meta Musee

New York City

Mar 2022 — Mar 2023

i work as a Al content creator for the metamusee, a curated art house with the pseudonym of 'lurgito'. over a year i work as the 'jack of all trades' of the organization. helping with my knowledge and soft skills to build art art content and educational conten in the era of NFTs.

Educator-English Teacher, DGCyE

Mar 2021 — Present

At the moment i'm working as a English teacher in a elementary school. I use my B2 English level to help children in second cycle of elementary school.

EDUCATION

IBM Data Analyst, Coursera

Mar 2023 — Jul 2023

i learn with the IBM Skill Network and use my knowledge to create a capstone real life project with the name of Technology trends and Data analysis. that resume and analyze the trends when choosing a Programming Language,centralization in the Programming world and other trends like the role of women in tech.

Data Scientist with Python, Datacamp

Apr 2023 — Present

at the moment i'm studying to be a Data Scientist. to develop models that help to solve problems. i'm developing a model to help Rio Negro's farmers to identify rotten fruit.

REFERENCES